Finding Aids to Personal Papers and Special Collections in the VMFA Archives Leslie Cheek, Jr. Personal Papers, 1931-1993 SC-02
VMFA Archives
- Series 6: Travel, 1952-1980; SC-02-06; 37 folders
  - Japan, October 17-December 1, 1966, Oct.-Dec. 1966 (Box SC-02 Box 14, Folder Folder 571)
  - National Trust trips, undated (Box SC-02 Box 14, Folder Folder 572)
  - New York cocktail parties, 1952 (Box SC-02 Box 14, Folder Folder 573)
  - South Seas Kungsholm Cruise, January 16-April 19, 1969, Jan.-Apr. 1969 (Box SC-02 Box 14, Folder Folder 574)
  - Gripsholm Cruise, June 25-August 11, 1965, June-Aug. 1965 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 575)
  - Around South America, S.A.L. Cruise, January 22-March 11, 1971, Jan.-Mar. 1971 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 576)
  - Around the World on the Gripsholm, January 23-April 19, 1973, Jan.-Apr. 1973 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 577)
  - Nielson, Dorothy S., 1971 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 578)
  - Scotland, Ireland, September 4-24, 1977, Sep. 1977 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 579)
  - Germany, Denmark, September 7-29, 1975, Sep. 1975 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 580)
  - Kingsholm, June 29, 1977, June 1977 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 581)
  - Alaska, July 1, 1973, July 1973 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 582)
  - National Trust trip-Venice, Palladion, September 1971, Sep. 1971 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 583)
  - London, Pan's theatre tour, December 21, 1969-January 6, 1970, Dec. 1969-Jan. 1970 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 584)
  - Gestadt, Switzerland, December 22, 1973-January 2, 1974, Dec. 1973-Jan. 1974 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 585)
  - Delta Queen, March 17-24, 1974, Mar. 1974 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 586)
  - Mississippi Queen, 1977 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 587)
  - Egyptian Cruise, January 10, 1975, Jan. 1975 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 588)
  - 1980 China trip (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 589)
  - New York to New England to Canada, May 13-27, 1980, May 1989 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 590)
  - Island world of Britain, May 25-June 11, 1979, May-June 1979 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 591)
  - Around the World, January 24-April 8, 1980, Jan.-Apr. 1980 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 592)
  - Madeira, February 1980, Feb. 1980 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 593)
  - R.E. Lee English trip, May 21-June 6, 1979, May-June 1979 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 594)
  - Friends of Winterthur, England tour, June 8-22, 1978, June 1978 (Box SC-02 Box 15, Folder Folder 595)